forexdailypips.com 2018-08-13

# Privacy Policy — ForexDailyPips.com

## Privacy Policy

**You may optout of your email list at anytime by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email received from ForexDailyPips.com. You may also email us at support@forexdailypips.com and ask to be removed from the email list.**

This privacy policy sets out how ForexDailyPips.com uses and protects any information that you give ForexDailyPips.com when you use this website.

ForexDailyPips.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ForexDailyPips.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * Email Address

What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Links to other websites**

Our website or promotional material emailed to you from ForexDailyPips.com may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

do not submit your personal information to us such as your email address whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website.

if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by using the unsubscribe link included in any email that you receive from ForexDailyPips.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to support@forexdailypips.com
